<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Save The Bird</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="explore_hooded_plover">Explore Hooded Plover</string>
    <string name="know_them_better">Know Them Better</string>
    <string name="natural_enemy">Natural Enemy</string>
    <string name="feather_color">Feather Color</string>
    <string name="life_cycle">Life Cycle</string>
    <string name="favorite_food">Favorite Food</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="feeding_period">Feeding Period</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="view_life_cycle_of_hoody">View Life Cycle of Hooded Plover</string>
    <string name="what_went_wrong">What Went Wrong?</string>
    <string name="report_sighting">Report Sighting</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect with NGOs</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="habitat">Habitat</string>
    <string name="habitat_answer">Beach/ Salt Lake</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="fact_1">Vehicles \nvs Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="fact_2">Kids and Pedestrians \nvs Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="fact_3">Dogs and Horses \nvs Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="fact_4">Only about 550 hoodies in Victoria</string>
    <string name="natural_enemy_answer">Red Fox, Herring Gull, Raven</string>
    <string name="breeding_season">Breeding Season</string>
    <string name="breeding_season_answer">August to February</string>
    <string name="incubation_period">Incubation Period</string>
    <string name="incubation_period_answer">30 days</string>
    <string name="nestling_period">Nestling Period</string>
    <string name="nestling_period_answer">13 days</string>
    <string name="clutch_size">Clutch Size</string>
    <string name="clutch_size_answer">1~3, usually 3</string>
    <string name="avg_size_weight">Average Size &amp; Weight</string>
    <string name="avg_size_weight_answer">21cm &amp; 95g</string>
    <string name="fact_title_kid">Kids and Pedestrians vs Hoodies</string>
    <string name="hp">Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="vs">vs</string>
    <string name="you">You</string>
    <string name="fact_content_kid">You must be thinking, “But kids are so cute! I wish I could run like them on the beach!”. Although did you know that they are one of the major threats for the Hooded Plovers? Sounds crazy, right? The Hooded Plovers’ tiny eggs are easy prey with the kids running and pedestrians walking on the beaches. \n\nHooded Plovers lay their nests right in the middle of the beaches so that they can have an all-round view on their predators. But the poor little birds face a tough time saving their eggs from these irregular predators, humans.</string>
    <string name="fact_2_title_1">Vehicles</string>
    <string name="a">A</string>
    <string name="fact_2_content">\t \t lovely sunny day and a road trip to the beach with family – sounds like a perfect day out! We all take our cars to the beach, don’t we? But did you know that around 80% of the Hooded Plover nests which are devastated are crushed by vehicles? Cars and off-road vehicles on beaches is a very common problem that these little birds face. Their tiny sized eggs and chicks make them very hard to see for the people driving. These vehicles on and near the beaches highly contribute towards the low breeding success of Hooded Plovers.</string>
    <string name="fact_title_dog">Dogs and Horses vs Hoodies</string>
    <string name="fact_content_dog">We all love to take our pets on the beach to get them some fresh air on their walks, right? And we also like to set our pets free off the leash so that they can enjoy their day out. But sadly, off the leash dogs also love chasing the Hooded Plovers and end up killing them. They also love to explore the beaches to hunt down their nests and eggs to trample them.\n\nSimilarly, horses on beaches also tend to trample these small eggs and nests. We might not realise these unfortunate things happening in the tiny birds’ lives on a normal day, but the poor Hooded Plovers face these difficulties regularly.</string>
    <string name="fact_title_status">Hooded Plover is Endangered</string>
    <string name="fact_content_status_1">This shy little creature, we affectionately call \'Hoody\', is a shorebird named Hooded Plover. Fifteen years ago, the terrible fact was that only 200 Hoodies were left, ringing alarm bells in Victoria. Therefore, BirdLife Australia has adopted a series of conservations to help the species return to Australian beaches.\n\nNotably, the survival rate of the Hooded Plover chicks is one of the lowest of all species, i.e. there is only 1 chick growing to an adult in every 100. Without human assistance, the survival rate of Hoodies from eggs to fully grown adults is only 2.5%.</string>
    <string name="fact_content_status_2">Up to 95% of nesting failures are due to unintentional beach behavior, such as dog chases hoodies near nesting areas; horse tramples the exposed nests on the beach; and even during breeding, increasing tourists make it difficult for Hooded Plovers to leave their nests safely and get food for their chicks.\n\nIt also results a unstable habitat that climate change leads more frequent tides and storms. Notably, inevitable natural enemies appear frequently, including red foxes, silver gulls, magpies and crows.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="home_page">Why Hooded Plovers are Endangered?</string>
    <string name="call_bird_life">Call for Birdlife</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="support_menu">Support</string>
    <string name="do_you_know">Do you know?</string>
    <string name="only_550">Only around 550 Hooded Plovers left in Victoria,\n where are 692 recorded beaches </string>
    <string name="use_app">Try using our app to help them</string>
    <string name="explore_link_1">https://birdlife.org.au/bird-profile/hooded-plover</string>
    <string name="explore_link_2">https://ebird.org/species/hooplo2</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore some facts</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming Soon ....</string>
    <string name="page_bar_home">\t\t\t\tExplore Facts about Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="page_bar_map">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Distribution of Hooded Plovers</string>
    <string name="page_bar_support">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Support </string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="mapbox_access_token">pk.eyJ1IjoibHd1dTAwMjEiLCJhIjoiY2tlZmYwcXR4MGsyODMzdXEyeGhlM21taiJ9.V4hkxkJ5mhH0NMCWoldlyw</string>
    <string name="fact_list_1">Only about 550 Hooded Plovers remain \nin Victoria, where 692 beaches are recorded. </string>
    <string name="fact_list_2">Hooded Plovers face threats from dog \nchasing and horseshoe trampling. </string>
    <string name="fact_list_3">For beach lovers: watch out for \nHoodies nests exposed on the beach. </string>

</resources>